Nada Ayuanda, S.E., Ak., M.Acc., CA., CPA.

Jl. Kelapa Lilin Utara IV DF 6 No. 9, Sektor 7C Gading Serpong, Tangerang 15810 08871303070 nada.ayuanda@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Holder of Certified Public Accountant and Chartered Accountant for more than 8 years experience. Member of Indonesian Institute of Public Accountants and Indonesian Institute of Chartered Accountants seeking to apply diverse accounting knowledge and experience with great professionalism and integrity. Posses a Master of Accounting from The University of Melbourne, Australia.

EDUCATION

The University of Melbourne (2011 - 2013)

Scholarship awardee for master program in Australia Master of Accounting

Trisakti University, Indonesia (2009)

The Professional Program in Accounting

UIN Syarif Hidayatullah Jakarta, Indonesia (2004 - 2009)

Bachelor of Accounting

WORK EXPERIENCE

Research Centre for HIV/AIDS UNIKA Atmajaya Jakarta Pusat Penelitian HIV/AIDS

Finance Manager

- Managing budget programs and projects
- Developing and managing financial system
- Supervising and assisting finance and accounting staffs
- Liassing with managerial staff and other colleagues
- Preparing and collating financial report

Universitas Bina Nusantara (2018 - Present)

Lecturer

- Financial Audit 1
- Financial Audit 2

rl

KAP Agus Ubaidillah & Rekan (October 2018 - Present)

Manager Audit

A medium sized accounting firm for audit and non-audit services

- Provided audit procedures that focusing on complex and/or specialized issues
- Reviewed the work of the associates during fieldwork
- Reviewed the audit cycles completed by associates
- Verified amounts and other information included in audit confirmations to audit work papers and inform Audit Senior on any discrepancies noted

KAP Ellya Noorlisyati & Rekan (March 2016 - June 2018)

Senior Auditor - Supervisor

A medium sized accounting firm for audit and non-audit services

- Provided a guidance to associates on audit schedules to be prepared and audit tests to be performed
- Reviewed the work of the associates during fieldwork
- Reviewed the audit cycles completed by associates
- Prepared and updated checklists for all audit request letters sent prior to commencement of the audit assignment and confirmations received thereafter
- Verified amounts and other information included in audit confirmations to audit work papers and inform

Audit Senior on any discrepancies noted

 Informed Audit Senior of any issues or observations gained during the audit field work and on any audit cycles

PPH Unika Atmajaya Jakarta (December 2015 - February 2016)

Accounting & Financial Consultant

Pusat Penelitian HIV dan AIDS Universitas Katolik Atmajaya

- Developed SOP (Stansdard Operational Procedure) for financial and accounting department
- Prepared financial report of PPH Unika Atmajaya using SANGO (Software accounting for NGO)
- Transfered accounting record from manual to accounting software

JICA - Japan International Cooperation Agency (November 2013 - October 2015)

Project Officer

Japan International Cooperation Agency - Project of Capacity Development for Green Economy Policy in Indonesia

- Supported the Indonesian Ministry of Finance and other related stakeholder for formulating fiscal recommendation to encourage the implementation of climate change financing in Indonesia in the sector of natural resources management, energy and agriculture
- Performed necessary duties as Project Officer and to support JICA experts and other project members in order to pursue the objective of the project, such as prepared the MOU for project consultant both national and local level.
- Maintained a communication and correspondence with relevant Indonesian counterparts, organizations and other donor for collecting information, demands and issues.
- · Submitted all project's activities report to JICA experts.

Black & Veatch

Junior Financial Consultant

Technical Advisory Service – Infrastructure Reform Sector Development Program

- Developed a financial feasibility studies, focused on water supply & sanitation, road, and transportation sector
- Analysed infrastructure finance and PPP development
- Consulted and reported the analysis result with senior consultant
- Delivered the analysis to National Development Planning Agency of Indonesia

Ellya Noorlisyati & Partner (2008 - 2010)

Junior Auditor

A medium sized accounting firm specialising in assurance services

- Interviewed a client to gather an understanding of the client's business processes, the control implemented in their day-to-day operations and also verifying that these controls are being performed.
- Attending a stock take to observe the company's methods for recording stock and test counting a sample of the company's stock items.

Bank Indonesia (January - February 2007)

Internship Program

A central bank of Indonesia

- Understanding the Standard Operational Procedure of Bank Indonesia, especially in accounting of foreign exchange division.
- Understanding the banking systems, such as RTGS (Real Time Gross Settlement) and clearing.

EXTRA-CURRICULAR EXPERIENCE

AIESEC (December 2012 - February 2013)

Volunteer Program

Feel Lanka Projectin Sri Lanka

- Worked in a team to make a market campaign for Sri Lanka Tourism
- Travelled and Stayed in some places in Sri Lanka to understand the culture of Sri Lanka
- Using photography skill to support the market campaign